movieberry.com 2013-08-18

# Download movies online. Watch online movies. Movies HD, DVD, DivX quality.

Privacy Policy

By registering on MovieBerry.com, you agree with the terms and conditions of using it. If you disagree with any clause of this Agreement, please be advised not to subscribe to MovieBerry.com. The Website Administration reserves the right to change registration procedure or the way the services are rendered. 

**IP address**  
Due to the Internet specifics, we have to collect the statistics on the Customers' IP addresses. This information helps us to deliver the best quality services that are particularly interesting for you. IP addresses collecting also helps us to identify and solve technical problems. MovieBerry.com takes all necessary precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

**Cookies**  
According to the Internet common practice, MovieBerry.com's Administration uses cookies. This helps us to understand which parts of our website are most popular and which services are highly demanded. Cookies are not used to elicit any private information such as the Customer's login or password. Disabling cookies may result in hampering your access to some of MovieBerry.com's resources. 

**Your personal information**  
Every time you refer to MovieBerry.com, the Website Administration gets access to your personal data on our Website such as lists of downloads, e-mail address, statistics, etc. Your personal data help us to keep you informed about new releases and events that you might be interested in. Your privacy is of the highest priority for MovieBerry.com, and we do our best to protect it. MovieBerry.com's Administration undertakes not to disclose any data without Customer's permission.

**Your financial information**  
When paying for the Website services, the Customer has to notify the Administration about the preferred payment method. The Website Administration do not disclose your payment details. The Website Administration undertakes to keep all other financial information confidential.
